[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111103pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["``", "NNP", "DT", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 12, "question": "Probably -- one of the \"Night at the Museum\" maybe?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ":", "CD", "IN", "DT", "``", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "''", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 13, "answer": "\"Meet the Fockers.\"", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111103pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 98, "question": "Where do you think the depth charge will come in the scandal if at all?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 99, "answer": "Well, that's the big question that we're all waiting for.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111103pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 113, "question": "What do you say to that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 114, "answer": "Well, we don't discuss our sources.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111103pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "VBG", "RP", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 124, "question": "Let me start with you, Randall Kennedy, is Herman Cain playing the race card or is the race card being played against him here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 125, "answer": "Well, to the extent that he has said that one of the reasons that this is coming up is because of race, it seems to me that he's using race as a propaganda weapon here.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Randall Kennedy", "Herman Cain"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111103pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 128, "question": "Larry Elder, would you agree with that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 129, "answer": "I think that's right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111103pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NNS", "WP", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 142, "question": "What do you make of that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 143, "answer": "Well, the people who like him like him a whole lot and I think that they are rallying to their man.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111103pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 152, "question": "Yes, it's been nonpolitical if you like, but there is something very human about Herman Cain which is resonating with people, isn't there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "CC", "EX", "VBZ", "NN", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 153, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Herman Cain"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111103pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "POS", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "WP", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "TO", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 170, "question": "I mean is there one rule for as some believe black conservative politicians and another rule for middle class white politicians?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "RB", "CD", "NN", "IN", "RB", "DT", "VBP", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 171, "answer": "No, I think what's shown is that, you know, people have their bases and people who like politicians are willing to close their eyes to, you know, deficiencies for their man.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111103pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 212, "question": "What is the idea of me?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 213, "answer": "Maybe it's not really you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111103pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 217, "question": "The need to delve deep in people's souls?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "POS", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 218, "answer": "I like doing that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111103pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 219, "question": "You do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 220, "answer": "And actually you like doing that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111103pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 237, "question": "Do you like the pressure of having to be funny?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 238, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111103pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["``", "NNP", "DT", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 245, "question": "Probably -- one of the \"Night at the Museum\" maybe?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ":", "CD", "IN", "DT", "``", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "''", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 246, "answer": "\"Meet the Fockers.\"", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111103pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 252, "question": "What did you do, Focker?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 253, "answer": "Nothing.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Focker"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111103pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 279, "question": "Advantage or disadvantage?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 280, "answer": "Well, it depends what you're talking about.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111103pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 285, "question": "But then there's also -- then you have to kind to make your own way and, you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "RB", "VBZ", "RB", ":", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 286, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111103pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 296, "question": "They'd be married 57 years?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 297, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111103pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 298, "question": "It's pretty amazing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 299, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111103pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "IN", "POS", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 312, "question": "Is that true?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 313, "answer": "No, that's true.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111103pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", ":", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 314, "question": "Are there some you don't let them watch?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 315, "answer": "Well, they -- first of all they're not that interested in watching my movies.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111103pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 320, "question": "Are they showing signs of comedic genius?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 321, "answer": "They are -- they're very theatrical children, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111103pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 322, "question": "Do you love being a father?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 323, "answer": "I love being a father.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111103pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 329, "question": "Yes, I mean, in terms of your filming schedule, how do you juggle that with being a dad?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 330, "answer": "You have to figure out how you're going to do it so that you make sure that you have the family time.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111103pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 335, "question": "I can't find the demons?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 336, "answer": "There's no darkness.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111103pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 345, "question": "Major drug abuse?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 346, "answer": "It's well hidden.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Brian Grazer"]}, "docId": "111103pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 355, "question": "Anything to chip away at the halo?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "TO", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 356, "answer": "Brian Grazer and I are having an affair.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111103pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 362, "question": "Is it going well?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 363, "answer": "I'm in love with his hair.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111103pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 390, "question": "Why are you laughing there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 391, "answer": "I was laughing that you always show the person watching themselves.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111103pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 401, "question": "\"Tower Heist\"?", "question_pos_tagged": ["``", "JJR", "NNP", "''", "."], "aSentId": 402, "answer": "I'm really excited because it's actually -- it's a genre of movie that I've never been in.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111103pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 428, "question": "What's going on with your country?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 429, "answer": "Oh wow.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111103pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "RBR", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "TO", "VB", "NN", "TO", "JJR", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 433, "question": "He disappointed you, Obama?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 434, "answer": "I -- I'm a -- I'm disappointed that we haven't seen more bold decisions from him and a willingness, I think, to maybe stick to more of what he had, in his campaign, had said in terms of what he was willing to do.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111103pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 453, "question": "I mean, why does it still motivate you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 454, "answer": "I went down there for the first time before the earthquake, and it was in such a bad situation that I wanted to try to do something to help there.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111103pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "POS", "VBN", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 458, "question": "What do you feel about people who criticize celebrities for helping the stuff like that, the criticism being you're just doing it to promote yourself?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "WP", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 459, "answer": "Well, I think everybody's entitled to their opinion.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111103pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 495, "question": "You must be sick of it, aren't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 496, "answer": "Not at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111103pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 497, "question": "Are you being honest?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "JJS", "."], "aSentId": 498, "answer": "Sometimes I'm sick of it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111103pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 505, "question": "-- with the passage of time?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 506, "answer": "Wait a minute.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111103pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 507, "question": "I'm affectionate toward the movie or the passage of time in general?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 508, "answer": "Both.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111103pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 522, "question": "Is this true?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 523, "answer": "Now it comes out.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111103pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 537, "question": "Any tantrums?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 538, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111103pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 565, "question": "-- monstrous, box office megastar?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "JJ", ",", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 566, "answer": "It's like a nightmare.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111103pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 567, "question": "For the worse in any way, a little chink in the armor that we could do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "RB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 568, "answer": "Not that I have found.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111103pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 588, "question": "Then what will you do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 589, "answer": "Die.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111103pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 602, "question": "You mean bad things about him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 603, "answer": "Things you've heard.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111103pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 606, "question": "Is he as -- is he as squeaky clean as he's trying to make out?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", ":", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 607, "answer": "As far I'm concerned, he is.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111103pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "EX", "VBZ", ":"], "qSentId": 615, "question": "Is anybody, do you think, in Hollywood, left who's got a better record than that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBD", "WP", "POS", "VBD", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 616, "answer": "I'm sure there's --", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Hollywood"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111103pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 619, "question": "Would he beat that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 620, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Brian"]}, "docId": "111103pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ":", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 669, "question": "How important is someone like Ben to a movie now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 670, "answer": "Put it this way: we developed the movie -- Brian and I developed the movie for several years.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ben"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111103pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 696, "question": "If it doesn't work out, it all becomes his fault?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "RP", ",", "PRP", "DT", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 697, "answer": "Not at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111103pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "JJ", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 710, "question": "And Brian had done maybe five, six movies with him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNP", "VBD", "VBN", "RB", "CD", ",", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 711, "answer": "Yes, total of six movies.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Brian"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111103pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "RB", ":", "DT", ",", "DT", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 726, "question": "Ben was not available?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 727, "answer": "Ben wasn't -- no, this was after we wrapped the movie.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111103pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 739, "question": "Did he -- did he, someone like you, feel intimidated?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 740, "answer": "Sure.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Eddie"]}, "docId": "111103pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 741, "question": "Working with someone like that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 742, "answer": "Yes, because Eddie has been -- he's iconic for, you know, the last 25 years.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111103pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 783, "question": "Get Leo in a dress?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 784, "answer": "We've got it.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Leo"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111103pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 789, "question": "(INAUDIBL) get people from the acting world together, I'm always fascinated who is the actor's actor, who's the one -- if you could cast one leading man in the last movie you ever make, who would it be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "CD", ":", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CD", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 790, "answer": "I can't do it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111103pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 802, "question": "Are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 803, "answer": "In a movie, my first movie role.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111103pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNPS", "."], "qSentId": 805, "question": "It is a Robert Zemeckis movie?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 806, "answer": "ORGAN: Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Robert Zemeckis"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111103pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 807, "question": "Is it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 808, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]